(Tongyeong, South Gyeongsang Province)
(A lush, green spring in May)
Yes, that's really cute.
(A pier in a fishing village)
(Yum Jung Ah, Roh Yoon Seo)
Wait.
(Kang You Seok, Kim Sun Young)
- You Seok looks so cute.
- Yes!
(Laughing)
(Giggling)
(Surprised)
- What?
- Are you leaving?
- What's going on? Hold on.
- Why?
What's going on here?
- What's happening?
- What?
What's this?
What's going on?
- Hey.
- Wait a minute.
- Wait...
- This can't be true.
- Seriously?
- Wait.
What are they doing?
Wait a minute.
- I'm hungry.
- No!
- Goodness.
- What do you do about them?
What are you doing?
Where are you going?
Gosh, they're so cruel.
Jung Ah.
(Fresh off the Sea 3)
I don't even see them anymore.
(A month ago)
I'm nervous.
- Really?
- Yes.
This feeling of starting something new.
Hey, Kim Sun Young.
Hello.
- Jung Ah.
- Yes?
You look pretty today.
I just came from home.
Don't lie to me.
I've been to your place, and you weren't dressed like that.
What are you talking about?
You're unbelievable.
My goodness.
- It hasn't been that long.
- Didn't you come...
to my house two months ago?
- It's only been 2 months?
- Was it less than 2 months ago?
(Meanwhile, someone arrives.)
You Seok, we were just talking about you.
- Should I come back later?
- Hello.
- No, come in.
- No.
- Hello.
- We know each other, right?
- Right.
- Really?
- We just...
- We met each other a while ago.
- We worked on something together.
- We met each other...
about four hours ago.
We'll be filming together two weeks later.
Hello, it's nice to meet you.
- Hello.
- Nice to meet you too.
- You've never met each other?
- No, it's our first time.
- We've never met before.
- Right.
I've seen her a lot...
- on TV.
- On TV?
(She finds him adorable.)
Do you know Yoon Seo?
- She and I were in a drama before.
- I see.
Then we all know each other.
I haven't worked face-to-face...
- with Yoon Seo, - Didn't you work together once?
but we were in a drama together.
(The youngest...)
(who's met everyone here has arrived.)
- Hello.
- Our youngest is here.
- What is it?
- What's that?
- Hello.
- Come in.
My goodness.
- It's been a long time.
- Yoon Seo, what did you bring?
She brought a present.
- Look at her.
- Hello.
- I haven't seen you in a long time.
- Have you been well?
Long time, no see.
- Hasn't it been years?
- Yes.
- Have you been well?
- It's good to see you.
We were so close before.
(The youngest who's attached to her)
What's all this?
Wait, let me explain.
Yesterday was Arbor Day.
- You're right.
- I've gotten into plants lately.
- Really?
- I picked out one...
that would suit each of you.
One that suits each person?
Based on the vibe?
I don't know if you keep plants,
but having one at home makes me feel good.
- Yoon Seo, you have a kind heart.
- Thank you.
My goodness.
I've only seen Yoon Seo 2 or 3 times...
- at movie premieres.
- During the "Smugglers" premiere.
Right, during the "Smugglers" premiere,
I went to say hello.
- Right.
- She came running all the way...
from a distance just to say hello.
- I heard that.
- We never worked together before.
Right.
- Jung Ah told me about that.
- She hugged me like this.
Every time I watched her on screen, I thought she was so beautiful.
When she came over to say hello, she was even prettier.
Thank you.
(Embarrassed by the compliment)
- This is great.
- Everyone knows each other.
We've met at least once.
I have so many questions to ask.
(Even though I know a lot about you, I have a lot to ask.)
Where's your hometown? What's your family like?
- Jung Ah.
- Yes?
- Okay.
- Yes.
- Can I...
- Really?
- Can I talk about myself?
- Sure.
I like talking about myself.
You start, You Seok.
About me...
My hometown is Gangneung in Gangwon Province.
I lived there until I was 19.
My grandfather was a farmer...
- when I was a kid.
- My gosh.
What did he grow?
- He mostly grew potatoes and rice.
- In Gangwon Province?
Those were his main crops.
- Rice?
- Then...
- Rice and potatoes?
- I've never had to buy rice.
That's real privilege.
Then you must be good at working in the fields and rice paddies.
Not really.
When I go help out, I'm just the snack assistant.
I bring them snacks.
(Far from working in the field)
- So you don't know how to farm?
- I'm clumsy.
- You have no farming skills?
- I have no farming skills.
Originally, I studied art.
I went to an arts high school.
- Sunhwa Arts School?
- How do you know?
I looked everything up.
Is that when you started studying art?
I also majored in fine arts in college.
- At Ewha Womans University, right?
- Yes.
You studied western painting.
Yes, I luckily got in.
That's great.
Yoon Seo is also famous...
for having a good fashion sense.
- No way.
- Really?
- Isn't it a bit overwhelming?
- How do you know so much about her?
(She's Yoon Seo's unofficial spokesperson.)
A lot of information came up.
- Maybe because I searched a lot.
- Really?
I heard that you really wanted to be on this show.
- Me?
- Yes.
Even though you were incredibly busy,
you wanted to make time for it.
- I did.
- To experience country life?
- What was the reason?
- It was...
watching Fresh Off the Sea 1 and 2.
I've been a huge fan of Jung Ah since I was young.
- I wanted to work with her.
- I should treat him...
- exceptionally well.
- I've admired her.
The moment I heard you were on it, I said yes without hesitation.
- Me too.
- But...
I also enjoyed watching Fresh off the Sea 1 and 2.
Seriously.
It was a show I've wanted to be a part of.
It was very healing.
(That's how people who truly love Fresh off the Sea...)
(and Jung Ah came together.)
I watched the entire season over 2 or 3 days until 4am.
I even paused it when I went to the bathroom.
I don't know why it was so important to watch you do every single thing,
but I still wanted to pause it.
I paused it, went to the bathroom, and put it back on.
I watched the whole thing in an hour.
It was that impactful in my life.
I made up my mind this time.
I'm going to live for the viewers.
(Is that so?)
You gave me so much comfort...
that I want to pass on that feeling.
- The comfort you received?
- Exactly.
- And I'll do my best.
- Yes, that's a good idea.
I'm curious to see how you guys are going to live together.
I'm the complete opposite of you.
(I sleep in and like to lie around.)
- All three of you? That's harsh.
- At least I am.
I'm the opposite of you.
- Why don't you ever take a break?
- Right.
- When you rest, I can rest too.
- I heard that you didn't rest.
- I'm not the type to lie around.
- I know.
You say, "Let's get some rest."
Then three seconds later, you're back on your feet.
- Then we have to get up with her.
- Right.
Are you all spontaneous types?
- You don't like spontaneous people?
- Are you a spontaneous type too?
(Smiling)
- Are you a spontaneous type?
- That's wonderful.
All of them are spontaneous.
I'm the type who follows planners really well.
- Me too.
- We love planners.
I'll be the only one making all the plans.
(Jung A realizes that road ahead won't be easy.)
Who's going to make the bed? The three of us will sleep together.
- I make the bed.
- I'll do it.
- Really?
- Yes.
I've never made my bed in my life.
Not once.
- What?
- Yes.
Seriously, I've never made my bed.
Have you? You'd better be honest.
Sometimes.
I can't say never.
- You make your bed when you get up?
- No,
- I rarely do it.
- See?
But I do it sometimes.
- What does this mean?
- When someone comes to visit...
You make your bed because...
- Exactly.
- someone is coming to your house.
But after sleeping...
This is going to be rough.
(She's getting shocked several times today.)
- But I'm quite obedient.
- Really?
Don't you prefer people who quietly follow along?
- Right.
- Instead of those who lead...
Without talking back?
- Without talking back?
I might talk back sometimes.
(Switching into playful mode)
I got it, you rascal.
(He's got some nerve.)
I don't think You Seok will be easy to handle.
- Right.
- He doesn't listen.
(The mischievous one loves getting attention from the older ladies.)
- You watched Fresh off the Sea.
- Yes.
From watching it, what did you want to try the most?
Playing games...
and making bets with the production crew.
What are you good at?
- What are you good at?
- I'm very curious.
- Are you strong?
- No, I'm not very strong.
I'm clever.
- You're smart?
- What kind of smart?
- Are you good with petty tricks?
- Exactly.
You're good at coming up with petty tricks?
That's great. You must be good at games.
Yes, I'm good at games.
- You're good at playing games?
- Yes.
When deciding who does the dishes,
- We should play a game.
- we should play a game.
We could make some money,
bet with...
- the production crew.
- Bet with them again?
- Then we can multiply the amount.
- Again?
- He's only thinking about games.
- We can multiply it.
Yes, that's a good idea.
We must come up with games that we can win.
Those that work in our favor?
- Yes.
- But they don't go the way we want.
What I'd like to do is earn money,
- buy ingredients, and cook.
- Make food?
I'd like to cook.
I'd like to cook for Jung Ah.
(Showing attention toward Jung Ah)
(She's the first person who wants to cook for Jung Ah.)
- She's such a good daughter.
- She really is.
It's because you end up cooking every time.
Jung Ah, why don't you take a break this time?
You're saying that because you haven't been out there yet.
- That's true.
- It's not that kind of situation.
All of us are dreaming now.
There's no time to relax and fool around.
I understand, Jung Ah.
- It's a war.
- It must be a battlefield.
Why? It was so comforting to watch.
(It's a war!)
(What will shake up the siblings)
- Why isn't it working?
- I can't lift it.
(A new battleground)
(Nature that refuses to compromise)
(A scale that has grown relentlessly bigger)
(Tougher than ever)
(More intense than ever)
(This time,)
(Fresh off the Sea will become...)
(something unlike before.)
(One month later)
(Tongyeong)
We have to start the engine.
I will try it for now.
(The production crew seems unusually busy today.)
(It feels like something is about to happen today.)
(Without a single suspicions,)
(a car pulls in.)
Hello, I look forward to working with you.
(Second Eldest Sun Young arrives first.)
I woke up so early...
because my heart was fluttering.
(While Sun Young is feeling nervous)
Hello.
(The siblings' 3rd eldest, You Seok arrives 2nd.)
- Gosh, look at him.
- This is great.
(Making his entrance with confidence)
Are you the first one to arrive?
You should've arrived first.
- There was some traffic.
- You Soon.
Yes.
- I told you to call me by my name.
- Yes, Sun Young.
Okay.
The viewers may not fully understand the situation yet.
The two of you, how do you feel?
I feel great. The weather is beautiful.
I don't know how long this will last, but...
I don't feel that great.
- Why?
- I feel the pressure...
to make the viewers happy.
(Sun Young only knows the viewers and nothing else.)
I'm determined to work hard...
for the next three days for the viewers.
I feel pressured.
(Youngest Yoon Seo arrives.)
Hello.
(She hugs Sun Young as soon as she arrives.)
Jung Ah. What did I tell you?
(Captain Yum is the last to arrive.)
You said that you'd dress up.
Do I look bad?
I didn't know what to do with my hair.
- Jung Ah.
- I did what I could... Hello.
Your hair looks nice today.
- My hair...
- You put it towards the front.
I didn't dry it completely.
- I don't know how to style it.
- It looks great right now.
We'll start with the poster shoot on the boat...
because the weather is nice.
(A poster photo shoot is scheduled on a boat today.)
Where should we go?
- Do we go in right away?
- Yes.
There must be a room assigned...
to each of us.
This is fascinating.
There's no name on it. Do we go in wherever we want?
(On the yellow, orange, red, and green bungalows)
(Instead of their names, cue cards are attached.)
Pick the color you want.
"Fresh off the Sea."
(The siblings pick a bungalow without the slightest suspicion.)
(Click)
I hope that there's a surprise waiting for us.
- Do we go in?
- Do we just go in?
Okay.
(They had no idea...)
(that this decision would decide their destiny.)
(While the siblings are getting changed)
Before that, we should...
(A suspicious strategy meeting is underway.)
(This boat isn't supposed to be...)
(for a poster photo shoot.)
(The poster the siblings are shooting for is fake.)
(The boat prepared for the photo shoot)
(In reality,)
(it's a fishing boat for work.)
(The photographer for the fake poster shoot is ready too.)
The cast is arriving. Please get ready.
(On standby)
Gosh. As expected, the sun at the sea...
Did you put the overalls over your pants?
- Yes.
- I took my pants off,
so it's refreshing.
(Laughing)
- Hello.
(Today's unsuspecting targets are entering.)
- Should we go...
- Yes.
- on the boat?
- Do you need a hand?
No, it's okay.
(They board the boat without a single doubt.)
Can you give me a hand?
Heave-ho!
(She steps onto the fishing boat with a powerful cheer.)
The boat is big.
Are we...
- In one line...
- Line up in a single line.
- Jung Ah.
- She's at the center.
(They start with a group photo.)
(Smiling)
(Laughing)
(They continue with the photo shoot completely unaware.)
They're very good. I knew it.
(Trying to set the mood)
(Despite the slightly awkward attempts to build excitement)
(The group photo shoot is completed smoothly.)
Could each of you hold a razor shell?
Yes!
- That's so charismatic.
- Seriously.
Isn't that "Smugglers?"
(Laughing)
(The 2026 version of movie "Smugglers")
Answer the phone with the razor shell.
Hello?
(Answering a call)
(Satisfied)
- Yes.
- That's cute.
(I'm in the middle of a shoot, so I'm busy.)
Here we go. One, two, three.
(10 minutes before the labor starts)
You look amazing.
The older siblings are done. The younger siblings, come in.
- That was fast.
- Shall I take this?
- We'll do this first.
- After the shoot?
Okay.
- That was...
- Where?
quite simple.
- Please go down.
- Okay.
(Since it's a fake poster photo shoot)
Should I go up? Or do you want to?
- Why don't you go up first?
- You go up.
(Feeling sorry for no reason)
(They're totally ready for the shoot.)
(The youngest members take it too seriously.)
Gosh, look at them.
(A bonus scene for getting the older siblings' attention)
(Laughing)
Yes, that's very cute. You Seok is so cute.
(Playful)
One, two, three.
You Seok is so adorable. My goodness.
(3 minutes before heading out to sea)
These look so fresh.
- I've never touched them live.
- Me neither.
(With their hands full of sea squirts,)
(the youngest ones settle into their seats on the boat.)
Undo the rope, please.
(Rushing)
(The operation begins.)
(Fumbling around)
(Mission complete)
(The hidden camera emerges.)
Lift it up.
Here we go. One, two, three.
(The cameras are set.)
That's very cute.
(Completely unaware of what's about to happen)
- You Seok looks so cute.
- That's cute.
(The engine turns on.)
(Surprised)
(Rumbling)
- What?
- Are we heading out?
- Are we leaving?
- Why?
- Hold on.
- What?
- Are we leaving?
(The fishing boat sets sail.)
- Why?
- Hold on.
- What's going on?
- What's happening?
What?
(In total panic)
(Even the managers are caught off guard by the sudden departure.)
- What's going on?
- Are they leaving?
(We're leaving.)
- Hey.
- Wait a minute.
- Wait, where's the director?
- Seriously?
- Jung Ah!
- Is this serious?
- Seriously...
- Wait.
What's going on?
- Is this serious?
- Hold on.
Are they leaving?
(The boat slowly drifts farther away from shore.)
- Is this for real?
- Seriously?
(Jung Ah is flustered by the first unexpected situation...)
(on Fresh off the Sea.)
- What?
- Oh, no.
(Oh, no...)
- Please help us.
- Aren't we working together?
I guess you guys are razor shells, and we're sea squirts.
(She still doesn't understand the situation.)
I thought that we were eating.
Jung Ah, we're hungry.
(Setting sail with shouts on an empty stomach)
Wait a minute.
What do we do about them?
What's going on? Where are they going?
What is this? It's so scary.
Gosh, they're so cruel.
- This is so harsh.
- Why...
I forgot that it was a variety show.
We didn't even bring a hat.
We're starting... My hat...
My hat is over there...
(He puts a life jacket on her instead of a hat.)
My hat is over there.
(The boat that kidnapped the youngest ones sets off.)
(Stunned)
(The siblings are unable to overcome the shock.)
This is unbelievable.
What kind of sudden goodbye was that?
- Was the poster shoot a lie?
- Are they really leaving like that?
Was the poster shoot a lie?
Jung Ah, the poster shoot was a lie.
What?
I thought the photo shoot was way too simple.
(Shocked)
Then who was the photographer?
That was...
(The photographer for Fresh off the Sea)
Did we do a photo shoot for the poster?
Jung Ah, it will be during the next shoot.
(Unlike the eldest, the second eldest finds it funny.)
Gosh, that's so hilarious.
This is really fun.
It's very funny.
I thought that someone made a mistake...
when the boat started to move.
- That's so funny.
- Seriously.
(Meanwhile, on the boat that kidnapped the youngest ones)
- Jung Ah!
- Seriously...
Sun Young!
- It was so funny...
- I don't see them.
I don't see them anymore.
(Exclaiming)
Whatever.
It will work out somehow.
It would've been funnier...
if we jumped off when the engine started.
- We should've jumped off.
- Is that why...
they told us to grab a lot of sea squirt?
- To keep our hands full.
- To keep us from running away.
To keep our hands busy.
(The clues they missed begin to come back to them.)
- You Seok.
- That's also...
It must be the bungalow we chose.
- What was your color?
- It was red.
- No.
- Was yours red?
Was yours yellow?
- Pick the color you want.
- Let's see.
"Fresh off the Sea."
(The siblings chose the rooms in the colors they liked.)
(On the cue card that You Seok took a photo of)
(There was actually a clue to today's fishing trip.)
(Fresh off the Sea)
(Today's fishing job chosen by the youngest ones)
(Sea squirt)
(That's why the youngest ones were kidnapped onto the boat.)
They promised us motion sickness medicine and breakfast,
but we got nothing.
This place is really...
the best.
(Exclaiming)
- You Seok, let's make sure...
- To get revenge.
- to get revenge someday.
- We have to get revenge.
- We really have to.
- I won't...
We can't let this slide.
They completely got us.
(As the youngest ones vow revenge)
(One month later)
(At the Siblings' House)
We've been thinking about it...
ever since we got taken onto the boat.
We can't be the only ones who get fooled.
(Madly determined)
We prepared this for a month.
I will keep trying.
Nobody, nobody, but you
(A revenge drama by the siblings is coming soon.)
An aquaculture farm.
(They arrive at a vast aquaculture farm.)
We must be here. The boat is speeding down.
- Isn't this an aquaculture farm?
- I think so.
(The fishing boat drops anchor.)
(Glancing)
(You Seok takes a look around the farm.)
- Gosh.
- What is it?
- My gosh.
- You startled me.
It's sea squirts.
- Where? I don't see them.
- They're here. Look.
- They're right below here.
- We saw them in photos yesterday.
(Today's job for the siblings, sea squirts)
(Tongyeong, home to the pristine waters of the southern coast)
Tongyeong's waters are clean,
and the surrounding environment provides the perfect conditions.
(Hidden beneath the warm spring sea of Tongyeong)
The best season for sea squirts is from March to May.
(The sea squirt, the harbinger of spring and flower of the sea)
This is when they taste the best.
We harvest about five tons per day.
They are shipped out...
to places like Busan and Incheon.
(They're sent to destinations all across the country.)
(The bright orange sea squirt blossoms are in full bloom.)
(Tongyeong's sea squirt)
Captain.
- Hello.
- You were so quiet until now.
- All right.
What did you come to do today?
- We don't know.
- No one told us.
But you took photos of the sea squirts.
You came to harvest sea squirts today.
You came to harvest them. Hurry and tie your hair.
(A captain with an unusual personality)
My goodness.
(Immediately getting ready for the day's work)
Do we take off all of them?
- You Seok, what do we do?
- Do we take off the entire line?
(Lurking beneath the sea)
- There are so many.
- Don't we need more people, sir?
There are four of us.
Four is enough.
(Worried that we won't be able to handle 1 portion each)
- All right, let's do it.
- Will you just stand there?
- Do you need help?
- Hurry up over here.
Okay.
(The youngest members found the perfect captain.)
- Come here. Let me show you.
- Okay.
(The sea squirt pole hanging from the aquaculture lines)
- This is how you undo it.
- Okay.
(The tightly secured sea squirt pole)
(Untying the knot)
(Careful not to let it slip)
(The captain's first demonstration for the youngest members)
Hold it tight.
(If you drop the pole, you will lose the sea squirts.)
- This is very heavy.
- Do I hold onto it?
Of course. You have to hold onto three.
You have to hold three of these.
- Lift it.
- It's so heavy.
- How is it possible? Wait.
- Lift it.
- Do it together.
- Do I really have to hold it?
(The reason why You Seok is struggling this much)
(Bending over)
(The weight of just 1 sea squirt pole)
(About 150kg)
(Countless sea squirts hang endlessly down into the sea.)
(The immense weight of the rope leaves him chuckle in disbelief.)
It's really heavy.
Sir, how should we...
Tie two ropes together like this.
I see.
(Tie two ropes, which weigh 300kg, together with a strong line.)
After tying the ropes together...
(Pull the 300kg of sea squirts toward the crane.)
(Next, hook the line onto the crane, and that's it.)
So, I should untie this...
Now, untie the knot like this.
(Yoon Seo observes how the captain unties it.)
(Skillful)
My, you're doing well.
Now, do it again with another rope.
(Captain, the problem is...)
Pull it out this way.
How do I lift this up, Captain?
- Okay. Two, three. Hold it.
- Oh, gosh.
Stop pulling it. Okay.
Hold this, okay?
- Oh, if I hold it...
- If you hold it...
- You should tie these together.
- Tie them together...
and hook the line onto the crane. Is that right?
(The captain and You Seok help her tie them with a line.)
All right.
Hook the line onto the crane.
(Yoon Seo tries to pull the ropes of sea squirts toward the crane.)
Oh, dear.
(Worried)
Oh, gosh.
(She staggers under the weight of the 300kg sea squirt ropes.)
This is insane.
(Letting out a bit of rough language, she succeeds.)
One more time.
(She's only done it once, but she's already sweating.)
So this is how sea squirts make it to our dinner tables.
- I didn't know it was so hard.
- I just realized...
that it wasn't easy at all.
- We've only eaten them.
- Right.
(Chuckling)
(Sea squirts keep coming endlessly, leaving them no time to rest.)
(The battle with the sea squirts feels like an actual war.)
It's so heavy.
My knee hurts.
(Groaning)
(Exclaiming in disbelief)
- Oh, gosh.
- Our very first task is not easy.
Hold on.
Seriously, it's still...
(The weight of the sea squirt ropes makes it even harder.)
(Hunching over)
Wait.
This is an absolute backbreaker.
(They continue working in a bent-over position.)
Gosh, my knee hurts.
(It's even more painful since she works on one knee.)
Leave it. And grab this one. Okay.
(It seems like he finally straightens his back.)
(But he staggers under the weight of the 300kg sea squirt ropes.)
(He's hunched over again.)
(It takes him such a long time to reach the crane.)
(He arrived.)
(Groaning)
(You Seok sees Yoon Seo struggling and returns right away.)
(Rushing)
Jung Ah and Sun Young would've...
I'm glad we're doing this, not them.
(Maybe it's a relief that they're not the ones doing this.)
(Sighing)
Hold on.
- That's a difficult one.
- Gosh, this knot is...
I made it.
(The dexterous Yoon Seo can untie a difficult knot as well.)
- I'll hold it for you.
- Hold this.
You can let it go.
After that...
(While she's at it, Yoon Seo tries to tie ropes with a line too.)
All right.
(Yoon Seo's handwork has become more dazzling.)
Okay.
(Yoon Seo's skills simply amaze You Seok.)
(The youngest members hook the lines on the crane.)
- The crane will haul them out now.
- Show me.
(Exhausted)
Are we going to strip all these off the ropes today?
That's a lot.
(The crane is on.)
(Surprised)
I can't see the end of it.
(The sea squirts are slowly coming up.)
(Surprised)
So we're going to...
- Should we strip them all?
- I can't see the end.
How many... My gosh.
What?
(Sea squirt tower)
(They finally show themselves, coming out of the deep sea.)
(Sea squirts, the flowers of the sea)
My goodness.
(It's taking a while to lift them up with the crane.)
(Now it makes sense why they felt so heavy.)
- You Seok.
- Move out of the way.
(The sea squirt tower weighing 1.8 tons)
You Seok, move aside.
No, wait.
(The sea squirt tower)
- My gosh.
- Oh, my.
(Shocked)
- Where should I go?
- It's huge.
Oh, gosh.
(Stretching 6m long, it's an overwhelmingly massive sight.)
They look like alien tentacles.
Look at them shooting water.
(The sea squirts are shooting the sea water.)
I've never seen so many sea squirts in one place before.
It feels like CGI.
(The reason why sea squirts are called the flowers of the sea)
It looks like a flower garden of sea squirts.
- Should we hook more of them?
- Yes, keep going.
- Yes.
Oh, we should do it again?
(Round 2 begins right away.)
Yes, Captain. Got it.
- Let's begin.
- We're doing it again right away.
I wonder what Jung Ah and Sun Young are doing now.
What do you think, You Seok?
(At the same time, the older members who were separated from them...)
(At the same time, at the bungalow)
I'm so sorry for them.
(Laughing)
(Yawning)
(The older members are chilling and relaxing in the bungalow.)
(They're lying on a mat because of their work clothes.)
I wonder what the others are doing now.
Can we really just rest here for two hours?
Just give us a task already if we're going to work anyway.
(Suspicious)
Why are you letting us do nothing?
Save your energy.
There's no way they'll just let us rest here and do nothing, right?
- There's no way.
- Right.
There must be a catch here.
(After that "kidnapping" incident, she developed strong distrust.)
There's definitely something.
- Oh, my.
- Thank you so much.
I'm surprised.
(Please have some tea while resting.)
You guys have changed so much.
- Thank you so much.
- This is weird.
Right?
(Should I drink this or not?)
- Thank you so much for this.
- It's a little reward.
You're giving us a reward...
- when we've done nothing?
- This is weird.
The fact that they prepared these tea bags is also suspicious.
Right.
I don't know what's going to happen, but it's going to be fun.
(The second oldest member gets another dopamine rush.)
Let's drink some tea since they gave us.
(The oldest member is still suspicious of the staff.)
(Laughing)
(The second oldest member finds this whole situation fun.)
Let's drink this since they gave us.
(Staring)
- I...
- Why did they put this here?
(It's just a sticker.)
What is this sticker doing here?
I mean, it's just the plastic packaging.
(Curious)
- Why did they put this here?
- Take a look at this.
- They put one here too.
- A red one.
They prepared these tea bags for us.
(Suspicious)
(What's going on?)
(While the older members are deep in their own conspiracy theories...)
This is fun.
(The sea squirt construction site)
(Oblivious to the youngest members' despair,)
(sea squirts keep coming up.)
(Chuckling in disbelief)
We'll have to strip all those off the ropes.
(Lost for words)
When they're all stacked up here.
(The sea squirts are dancing as if they were teasing the members.)
(Looking around nervously)
- My knees...
- Shall we...
- Maybe we need knee pads.
- ask them to call it a day?
- Hurry up and untie the ropes.
- Yes, sir.
Yes, Captain. Got it.
(That won't happen!)
Should we pull them all out?
All right.
(They lock in on the job immediately.)
While watching the captain doing this,
- I picked up a few tricks.
- You did?
Shaking the rope a little bit...
makes it easier to untie the knot.
Right, sir?
(Yoon Seo has mastered tying the ropes with a line.)
(It's a piece of cake now.)
Can you hook it onto the crane? Shall I do it?
Please do it for me. I'll untie those.
Ouch.
(You Seok, the older one, will move the heavy sea squirt ropes.)
(Delivery coming through!)
(The delivery is complete.)
(When You Seok returns after the sea squirt delivery...)
(Yoon Seo packs the sea squirt with a string.)
This should go that way.
Nice. You guys are good at this.
(He moves the sea squirts packaged by Yoon Seo.)
(He delivers them toward the crane.)
(You Seok is an experienced deliveryman.)
(The deliveryman struggles while groaning and sweating.)
(It will take some time due to the immense weight.)
(Panting)
(He's completed the sea squirt delivery.)
(They're working like a machine now.)
Impressive. You're good at this.
(A small word of praise for the newbies)
I can pull off some tricks now.
I'm getting the hang of this now.
(They're getting into the groove of the sea squirt harvest.)
(The tasks were entirely new to them as they'd never done them before.)
Oh, it's working.
- Gosh, my back hurts.
- Gosh, it's so heavy.
Are you okay?
- It's really heavy.
- You're doing so well.
Okay. All set.
(They're figuring out the way to tackle their tasks.)
The last one.
- The last one.
- Okay. Let's go.
- Okay.
- The last one.
All right.
Okay.
We're done.
(The deck was empty, but now it's filled with sea squirts.)
- It's done now, isn't it?
- Will we do it again?
- Go on in.
- Shall we start stripping them off?
- Okay.
- Go on in.
(Sunken eyes)
(Glancing)
(She massages the exhausted You Seok's shoulder.)
We're heading back with a fully loaded deck.
Right. It was still manageable.
Right, You Seok?
My knee hurt, but it was still manageable.
But I shouldn't say something like this.
(Where is this boat with sea squirts headed?)
(Meanwhile, at the port...)
Look at the sea squirts.
I see some people working over there.
- Where?
- Over there. I bet we'll do that.
I'm sure there will be a task for us.
(The youngest members are back on the land after the harvest.)
The boat with our members is coming in.
(Along with the members, today's workload is pulling in.)
- Guys!
- Hey.
- Hey, guys.
- Guys.
Guys.
(After their forced separation, they reunite with the older members.)
(We harvested this many sea squirts.)
- Great job.
- Sun Young.
- My goodness.
- Oh, my. Look at this.
- This is fascinating.
- Did you harvest all of these?
What did you guys do while we were gone?
- We did nothing.
- What?
You did nothing?
Was it hard?
- I thought...
- You did nothing?
you were harvesting razor shells.
It must've been exhausting.
(Crying)
(Comforting)
We're not done yet. We have to hook them onto the crane.
(They still have to unload all these sea squirts.)
There's more.
All set.
(They hook the lines onto the crane again.)
- I didn't know... It's massive.
- It's fascinating, isn't it?
It's fascinating.
This is my first time seeing how to harvest sea squirts.
(The older members have never seen a sea squirt bouquet like this.)
They look like flower garlands.
(Sea squirt garlands)
- They look like hanging flowers.
- Right.
(The 1.8 tons of sea squirts hanging from the crane...)
(will be kept under the sea to stay fresh.)
- Now that we've harvested them, - Yes.
- all that's left is...
- Yes.
- to sort them and sell them.
- Understood.
- I see.
(At this place where the siblings are,)
(all the freshly harvested sea squirts gather.)
(The sea squirt sorting station)
(Sea squirts, today's stars)
(They're making their entrance, flaunting their gorgeous color.)
(1. Separation of sea squirts)
(Passing through the separator,)
(the sea squirts are split into individual pieces.)
(Squirting water)
(The sea squirt water guns are shooting water everywhere.)
(The separated sea squirts are now moving on to the next step.)
(2. Removing debris)
(Split the sea squirt bunches that the separator missed.)
(Next, remove debris from the separated sea squirts.)
(3. Washing and sorting by size)
(Wash the sea squirts cleanly.)
(The smaller sea squirts slip right through the gaps.)
(4. The final sort and quality check)
(Sea squirt)
(Sort out the smaller sea squirts that the machine missed.)
(Keep the smaller sea squirts separately.)
(5. Completing the final sort)
(Only the ones selected through the process are shipped out.)
(Shall we start the sort now?)
Since the younger ones worked hard out at sea,
- do the easier job over here.
- Oh, yes.
Since the older ones rested, do the harder job over here.
I'll go over there.
- Here's what you should do here.
- Yes.
I think we have to sort the sea squirts.
You have to split the sea squirts that are stuck together.
There are still some sea squirts that the machine failed to separate.
- I see.
- Some are still stuck together.
You just have to separate them.
- As for you guys...
- Yes.
This machine sorts out the smaller sea squirts.
- So you have to sort out...
- Yes?
the smaller sea squirts that the machine missed.
- Should we sort out smaller ones?
- You just have to take them out.
- Yes, that's right.
(Jung Ah, who finished preparing to work...)
(Peeking)
(She carefully observes the seasoned workers.)
(Sun Young joins her.)
I see that they weed out the bad ones and put them in here.
(They've figured out how to get the job done.)
(They get to work right away.)
(Separating the sea squirts without hesitating)
(Jung Ah moves her hands quickly as an experienced member.)
(She spots the sea squirts that are stuck together.)
(She takes care of them once she spots them.)
(Separating)
(Once she starts working, she splits the sea squirts like crazy.)
(This is how an experienced member works.)
(What about Sun Young, who's standing next to Jung Ah?)
(Jung Ah already scanned everything here with her radar.)
(There are no sea squirts that are stuck together.)
I had absolutely no idea how sea squirts are prepared.
This is fascinating.
I really like sea squirts.
I had no idea sea squirts went through a process like this.
(Jung Ah doesn't even have time to talk.)
I had no idea sea squirts had roots just like wild ginseng.
They have roots.
- They look like wild ginseng.
- Right.
They don't smell like sea squirts, Jung Ah.
We have no time to sit around smelling them.
Exactly. Sea squirts have a great scent.
But I guess they don't have that scent just yet.
I should just toss the ones we can't sell, right?
Okay.
(Sighing)
- She's driving me crazy.
- What about this one?
Should I throw it away? I see.
(Chuckling)
(While Sun Young is into sea squirts...)
Pass. This one too. And that one.
- They all pass.
- I don't see any small ones.
Right.
- The machine sorts them out.
- Right.
The machine sort them out automatically.
Pass.
(The pre-sorting process makes their job easier.)
- This one.
- I found a smaller one.
(He found one smaller sea squirt.)
You did a great job out at sea.
- So I gave you an easy task.
- Thank you.
This is so easy.
- Did you have fun?
- What should I do with this one?
- I had so much fun. Yes.
- Did you?
- Here.
- It was really fascinating.
When can I ever experience something like this?
(The second batch of sea squirts, weighing 1.8 tons, is added.)
(The entrance is packed with sea squirt customers.)
(The older members are busy welcoming the sea squirt customers.)
That's good.
Koreans always prioritize speed in their jobs.
- Right.
- Speed is important.
Hurry up.
(They pick up the pace to get it done quickly.)
Oh, my goodness.
(Separating)
(It's no problem for Captain Yum.)
(The sea squirt separating machine)
(The sea squirts are split quickly by Jung Ah's skillful hands.)
(Sun Young works hard to keep up with Jung Ah.)
(Groaning)
(Struggling)
(It's harder to split sea squirts than expected.)
(Pulling hard)
Oh, boy. What should I do with this?
(Separating sea squirts is no joke.)
I can't split them.
My gosh. Here we go.
Hold on.
(She barely managed to split them.)
Oh, no. We have too many sea squirts...
that are stuck together.
(The sea squirt bunches that haven't been separated)
(The sea squirts are moved backward.)
Oh, we can just push them back when they're still stuck together.
We're backed up with work because of these clumps.
Our work is piling up.
(They need to move their hands more quickly.)
(On top of that, a 1.8-ton batch of sea squirts is added.)
(They separate the sea squirts non-stop as they keep pouring in.)
(Sea squirts are moved backward.)
We're so backed up.
- Oh, no. What do we do?
- My goodness.
We're falling behind. We need to pick up the pace.
Oh, no. This is bad.
- This is bad. We're in trouble.
- We really need to move faster.
What do we do?
(As sea squirts keep pouring in from both sides...)
(Screaming)
Hold on. Hang on a second.
(Captain Yum goes out of control.)
Jung Ah, we should move faster. Hold on a second.
I'm working as quickly as possible.
(The youngest members seem relatively relaxed.)
It looks like a chicken drumstick.
Now that you said that, it does look like a drumstick.
Most young people don't like sea squirts.
They have a strong scent of the ocean.
You should eat this if you want nice skin.
- Does it help to get nice skin?
- That's why you have nice skin.
I'm 80 years old.
Really? You're 80 years old?
I thought you were in your 50s.
You have a way with words, You Seok.
She really looks much younger than her age.
(He's socially savvy.)
I look like I'm 100 years old without a mask.
- No way.
- I look like I'm 100.
(He has a nice chat with the lady with a baby face.)
- This feels like a video game.
- Exactly.
- Like the carp bread tycoon game.
- Right.
(The youngest members are in full gamer mode.)
(Peeking)
You see...
Jung Ah and Sun Young seem so exhausted.
- We're falling behind again.
- Guys.
- Is it going well?
What? Well, we... Yes.
- We're falling behind again.
- Is it going well?
(She stammers out a yes.)
- It's chaotic here.
We keep getting the sea squirts sent back.
(Walking slowly)
- Do you need help?
- Sorry?
(Worried about the older members, You Seok steps in to help.)
I have to remove things like this and toss it, right?
That's right. That's what you should do.
You have to check the sea squirts thoroughly.
We kept getting the sea squirts sent back.
(The three of them work hard checking the sea squirts.)
This is much harder than what I did over there.
They're flooding in.
(Sea squirt)
Ma'am, you have amazing concentration.
- I've been doing this for 30 years.
- Yes?
- Thirty years?
- Yes.
(Surprised)
You've been doing this for 30 years?
(The lady is a veteran worker with 30 years of experience.)
Oh, I'm working with a master.
That's why you're so skillful.
Stop. Oh, no.
(I'll do my best too.)
(Beeping)
(The sea squirt basket is full.)
(She meticulously picks up the sea squirts which fell out.)
(Careful not to topple it over)
Let's go.
(She puts the heavy basket in its place.)
(Thanks to Yoon Seo, the basket starts to fill up again.)
(She spots something.)
More and more sea squirts are coming up.
They're rushing in.
(More sea squirts rush in.)
They're coming.
(Bottomless refill of sea squirts)
(They move their hands nonstop as they focus on sorting them out.)
Let's go peel sea squirts.
- What did you say?
- What was it?
We need to go peel sea squirts.
- Peel them?
- Yes.
(This wasn't the end of the task?)
- What was it?
- We need to go peel sea squirts.
- Peel them?
- Yes.
(This wasn't the end of the task?)
(The sorting facility they're working at)
(Next to the sorting area,)
(there's another workspace.)
(The job doesn't end with sorting them.)
(Pour out the whole basket of sea squirts.)
(It's time to peel them.)
(Peeling sea squirts is the final part of the labor.)
Let's go.
(After sorting the sea squirts, they're dragged without resistance.)
Let's cut it together.
How do I peel it?
The two things over here are the sea squirt's nose.
(Step 1. Find the sea squirt's nose.)
Cut it like this.
(Step 2. Cut its nose.)
(Cut right at the nose.)
You'll see its feces, the poo.
(Sea squirt's poo)
You need to remove it.
(Step 3. Remove the sea squirt's poo.)
(Sea squirt's poo)
Just score it, and it'll be removed when it's washed.
(Just score it, and it'll be removed when it's washed.)
- This poo.
- Yes. You need to remove the poo.
- I removed it.
- Good.
(Step 4. Put it into the container, and it's done.)
Okay.
- Like this.
- Score here.
Remove the sea squirt poo.
This one.
- That's right.
- Okay.
I got the hang of it.
(Captain Yum cranes her neck to stare at the sea squirt.)
(Very focused)
(She cuts its nose with precision,)
(and as she was taught, she takes it out...)
(and diligently removes its poo.)
- Is it here? It's here, right?
- That's right.
Yes, that's right.
(Fascinated by her first experience of peeling a sea squirt)
It gushes out when I cut it.
This is cathartic.
- What?
- Cathartic.
(Humming)
(He got curious while peeling the sea squirts.)
How do people eat this? As raw fish?
- Raw fish over rice?
- The old lady told me earlier...
that they have it as sea squirt bibimbap.
Yes.
- Sea squirt...
- Sea squirt bibimbap.
- We eat it raw too. With chojang.
- As raw fish?
(Is Yoon Seo doing okay?)
(Pretty skilled)
I got the hang of it now.
(Learning completed)
- Did you, Yoon Seo?
- Yes.
But I can't match up to the boss' speed.
(Laughing)
- Can I watch?
- Yes.
(3 seconds only)
(Jaw dropped)
That took her three seconds.
It would be over very soon if we worked at her speed.
(Deeply moved)
(Motivated by the demonstration, she peels diligently.)
(Skilled)
I can now see where the poo is located.
Just score it, and it'll be removed during the wash.
(Yoon Seo has adapted to it perfectly.)
(Skilled mode activated)
(Yoon Seo's container gets filled up quickly.)
(It's already almost full.)
- You're fast.
- I did a lot, didn't I?
Did the boss help you?
- Why do you have so many?
- No, she didn't.
You peeled a lot.
- She didn't help me.
- Yoon Seo peeled a lot.
You're good.
- I am, aren't I?
- You're talented.
(Proud of herself)
You've been doing well since just now.
It looks like she's good with her hands, no matter the task.
(Bopping to the compliment)
(1 box completed so far)
(Here are additional sea squirts.)
(The fight against sea squirts is ongoing.)
(Hunched neck)
(Stiff shoulders)
(The whole body aches from working with their necks bent.)
Your neck hurts from this.
(He stretches when he hears that.)
- Because you have your neck bent.
- Your back too.
- Straighten your back.
- You must be too focused on...
finding the poo.
- Yes.
- Staying standing is hard.
- Oh, no. Get a chair.
- Don't your feet hurt?
I'm always standing at home too.
I see.
- You don't stand much, do you?
- No.
- I'm normally laid down.
- Would you like to sit and work?
I'm sorry I'm the only one sitting down.
- If it hurts, you should sit.
- Yes. You should sit and work.
Aren't you tired, Jung Ah?
I'm used to this.
I do this even at home.
You're amazing. So cool.
- Stand more on a regular basis.
- I will.
I shall do that from now on.
Poo.
- Sir.
- Yes.
I'm too tired.
I'll pay you half the rate since you sat down.
We need 200 dollars to eat out.
I've been watching you, and all you do is talk and not work.
That's not true.
Come on, I introduced you to this job. You can't do this to me.
I introduced you to this job because you couldn't find one.
This is so fun. It's like watching a daily drama.
You cried and begged me to find you a job.
When did I ever cry?
You begged me so pitifully that I recommended you to the boss.
The boss initially said no because you were too old.
- What's this got to do with age?
- I...
I had to persuade the boss, you know.
You said you'd treat me well.
(The audience has great fun watching it.)
And you said you'd be fast, that you were good at finding poo.
"Good at finding poo."
This lady here is so talkative.
Ma'am, go home.
(In the end, the boss sends her home.)
I can't. I need to earn money.
(Crying)
You need to finish all of these.
(They must meet the target to be fed and paid.)
I'll provide you with a meal only then.
I'm hungry.
- This is done.
- We finished three boxes.
Good job.
- Thank you.
- Captain, I worked on this much.
Nice, you can put it down. It's the long-awaited mealtime.
Let's go eat.
Wait for me.
(Let's go to eat.)
Come this way.
Goodness.
It's food. Let's eat.
- It looks delicious.
- My gosh.
(A meal prepared on the boat for the exhausted siblings)
My gosh.
It looks delicious. I feel happy.
You all worked so hard today.
Tongyeong is known for three dishes.
Three dishes?
First, we'll have dried radish greens soup.
- Dried radish greens soup.
- It's boiled with ground eels.
Eels?
It's like loach soup with dried radish greens.
- It looks delicious.
- My gosh.
- It looks so good.
- And...
- Next is honey bread.
- Honey bread.
I love honey bread.
And the protagonist always appears last.
- Sea squirt.
Some people might not have tried it at all,
but no one has only tasted it once.
Once you eat sea squirt, you'll keep craving it.
You've worked hard, so enjoy your meal.
- Then we'll resume work.
- Okay.
- Make sure to eat up.
- Yes, thank you.
- Enjoy your meal.
- Thank you for the food.
They look delicious. I feel happy.
I was craving rice. It looks good.
I was so hungry.
(Warm and filling dried radish greens soup...)
(comforts their empty stomach.)
(Humming)
It restores your energy.
(A big bite)
(This is it.)
It's like loach soup.
Yes, they used eels.
It's not too fishy.
(Slurping)
This is nice.
It's so good.
- It's so good?
- Yes.
(Sniffing)
Add Korean mint here? Interesting.
- It's like loach soup.
- Yes.
(After blowing it, she takes a big bite.)
- Have you tried it before?
- I've tried it once.
- It tastes good.
- You've tried it once?
(Slurping dried radish greens soup)
I don't know.
Korean mint? What is Korean mint?
It's quite strong.
(Following Sun Young, she adds some Korean mint.)
(Taking a careful sip)
(It's good.)
- It's good.
- Yes.
- Korean mint...
- It's sharp.
- tastes a bit like tom yum kung.
- It tastes like tom yum kung.
- A bit, right?
- The ginger taste.
The spices.
- It tastes like tom yum kung.
- Really?
- A bit, right?
- Is it because of the powder?
It really tastes like tom yum kung.
(It's charming.)
(It's perfect for her.)
- Eels.
- Dried radish greens soup...
with eels.
- Yes.
- Eels.
(Entranced)
(The meal tastes like honey after the hard labor.)
It's good.
(Ma'am.)
Ma'am. Since I gave you your meal,
you'll work hard, right?
(No doubt about it.)
Right?
You've nothing left to complain about, right?
Thank you, boss.
(Laughing)
- You need to work hard now.
- Okay.
I'll work really hard.
You do hold some power.
- I prepared it all.
- I didn't know.
(This is funny.)
(It's time to meet the protagonist.)
(She dips fresh sea squirt into chojang.)
(She smiles as soon as she eats it.)
Amazing.
The meat is...
- This is good.
- I'll try it.
(Plump sea squirt)
The meat is extraordinary.
- Really?
- Yes.
It's good.
(The sea scent which spreads in her mouth makes her happy.)
(Youngest Yoon Seo has a bite of sea squirt too.)
(Tapping)
- Is it good?
- Sea squirt tastes good.
Sea squirt tastes good.
You can taste the sea.
(She strongly recommends sea squirt.)
- Right?
- Try it, You Seok.
- Dip it in chojang. It's good.
- When you eat it...
The sea taste.
(The flavor of sea explodes in his mouth.)
- You eat so well.
- I'm eating silently.
(Yoon Seo is in love with sea squirt.)
- You eat so well.
- I'm eating silently.
I'm so hungry.
You're eating, yet you still feel hungry?
Yes. I'm still hungry.
- I really...
- It's perfect?
I really needed this.
Seriously, Jung Ah.
This is the first time I felt so happy about getting food.
They always give you good food.
A meal after labor is so delicious.
I agree.
This is why you must work.
You must work.
Exactly. It tastes so good when you're hungry from work.
It feels so good to eat after working.
(After the happy mealtime ends)
- Let's work hard.
- Sea squirt.
We can do it.
- I think we can do it.
- Yes.
Eating gave me some energy.
Yes, that's why you need to eat.
(Cutting sea squirts a lot faster)
I'm going at a very fast pace.
Let's buy coffee.
- Let's buy coffee.
- Let's buy some coffee too.
(Let's earn the shipping fee.)
(Peeled)
(Yoon Seo's container is full.)
(Starting with Yoon Seo,)
(they add their shares one after another.)
(Peeled sea squirts are getting piled up.)
Didn't you empty out your container...
- just now?
- Yes.
(Yoon Seo's container is quickly filled up again.)
You're good. And fast.
Yoon Seo is amazing.
(Genuinely impressed)
You're really good.
She's our ace.
(The siblings' ace worker, Yoon Seo)
- You have great hands.
- Don't bother.
(They continue to peel excitedly.)
We did a lot, didn't we?
Yes, we did.
(They're almost seeing the end of it.)
Done!
- Done!
- Amazing.
- Goodness.
(Sea squirt labor is finished.)
Goodness.
Goodness, we're done.
(Around 1,000 sea squirts peeled)
Thanks for your hard work on peeling sea squirts.
Here it is.
(Here's the shipping fee.)
- How much is it?
- One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight,
- nine, ten.
- Nine, ten.
It's 100 dollars.
(As a bonus)
(For them to enjoy Tongyeong's unique eating-out culture)
(They get a Tongyeong-style seafood bar pass.)
(Proud)
A hundred dollars?
We'll make sure to enjoy it for the sake of the viewers.
Thank you for your hard work.
- Thank you.
They're sea squirts you collected yourself.
- Here.
He gave us so many.
(Sea squirts fresh off the sea)
- Good job today.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, boss.
(The sea squirts the siblings worked hard on)
(Containing the flavor of the fresh sea,)
(they were shipped off to all over the country.)
It must be the red car.
(A stunning new car!)
- It's stunning.
- It's nice.
(Groaning)
(You Seok will drive them home today.)
Good job today, everyone.
Good job.
(Hard work is over. It's time to go home!)
Shall I start?
- Let's go.
Let's stop by a supermarket on the way.
- For grocery shopping?
- Yes.
(Let's go grocery shopping on the way.)
We have 100 dollars.
We're rich.
(Busy)
(Meanwhile, Yoon Seo's hands suddenly became busy.)
Groceries list.
First, thin-sliced pork belly.
- Thin-sliced pork belly.
- Yes.
Let's buy one radish and cabbage kimchi too.
We definitely need kimchi.
Let's cook sea squirt doenjang jjigae.
- That sounds so good.
- Nice.
Potatoes.
Onions.
Potatoes, onions.
Green onions.
(A pause)
- Tofu.
- Tofu, zucchini.
- Doenjang.
- We have doenjang.
The sea is so pretty.
Look to your right. It's so pretty.
It's pretty.
(The blue sea unfolds outside of the window.)
This is so pretty.
- It's so nice and pretty.
- Oh, my.
It's cute.
It's really pretty here.
It has a really pretty color.
(Following the outstretched coastal road)
I love the view.
(The four siblings drive freely.)
It's so pretty.
That line.
Isn't that the one?
- A cable car?
(A cable car?)
(Cable car)
It looks fun. There's a lot to do in Tongyeong.
(Tongyeong's fun activities, cable car and luge)
I want to ride both a cable car and a luge.
It looks so fun.
- It looks so scary.
- It's safe.
Is that the cable car...
- with the transparent floor?
- Exactly.
- Goodness.
- I've ridden it many times already.
Really? You must not be scared of those.
- Well, you just...
- Doesn't it look fun?
I'm actually a scaredy-cat too.
- Really?
- He's a scaredy-cat.
I'm bad with rides too.
You know, the feeling of your organs flying up.
Yes. I like rides because I like that feeling.
- Really?
- What?
- That gives me chills.
- I...
- But that much is fine, right?
- Yes.
You Seok must really want to ride the cable car.
You want to ride it.
Let's go.
(The siblings have arrived at a supermarket.)
It's huge.
- This supermarket is big.
- It's really big.
Hello.
Shall we buy some snacks too? Do we have enough money?
- We should buy snacks too.
- That sounds good.
- Shall we buy 30 eggs?
- Yes.
We can fry them for breakfast tomorrow.
Dear viewers,
we'll be having chungmu gimbap for breakfast tomorrow.
There's a camera here too.
Dear viewers, I'm not doing this because my back aches.
- She...
- Tomorrow breakfast...
I want to push the trolley, that's all.
Dear viewers, I'm not doing this because my back aches.
"Dear viewers."
She's like this. "Dear viewers."
I'm pushing the trolley.
My back doesn't hurt.
(Please trust me, viewers.)
(Looking around)
(Meanwhile, Yoon Seo is going through the list.)
Tofu for jjigae.
(How Secretary Roh grocery shops smartly)
It's 99 cents.
(Step 1. Compare the prices carefully.)
It's here, 99 cents.
Jung Ah, thin-sliced pork belly is here.
That's from Chile, that's from the US.
Okay.
Don't just go for it because it's cheap.
This...
- Buy it.
- Still...
- Let's buy Korean pork.
- Yes.
Thank you.
- Is it time for snacks?
- Yes.
(He picks up a sweet snack.)
I like this.
(He picks up a salty one this time.)
Will two snacks be enough?
- We might go over the budget.
- Yes.
Okay.
- Thank you.
(Grocery shopping cleared neatly thanks to smart Secretary Roh)
Let's go.
- It's nine minutes from here?
- That's near.
I can't wait to see the house.
- I'm curious.
(I'm curious.)
Whenever I watched the show on TV,
I went, "The house is pretty."
I never imagined I'd visit the house myself.
Jung Ah, we'll be cooking dinner later in the evening.
What do we do before that?
- We should have a house tour.
- You're right.
And check out what's around the house.
In 500m, turn left.
Next, in 110m, turn right.
I thought it said "Because it's Dex."
Really?
(Dex...)
(all of a sudden?)
In 300m, turn left.
Next, in 110m...
- Heard that?
- It said in 110m, not Dex.
"Because it's Dex."
I've seen him so many times.
I have this sense of closeness too.
- Can Dex come again, Jung Ah?
- Exactly.
I want to meet him.
Can't you be satisfied with me?
How can you talk about Dex when You Seok is here?
I don't know who Dex is.
I thought you were Jekyll and Hyde.
"No."
(Getting tense)
- Next, in 110m...
- I want to see him.
It says "because it's Dex" again.
- I should switch off the GPS.
- In 110m.
- He's boiling up.
- This won't do.
Who is Dex?
- The person you like.
- Who is that?
Gosh, what are you saying?
I only know You Soon and You Seok.
Straight down the road, we should arrive at our house.
(They've arrived at the entrance of the village!)
It's so pretty here.
It's the village hall.
- It's pretty.
- We must be almost there.
I love a village like this.
It's right in front of the sea.
(With the blue sea as the front yard,)
(it's a friendly fishing village full of the sea air.)
(Flowers bloomed on the walls...)
(welcome you with open arms.)
(It's Sopo Village, Tongyeong, which smells of flowers.)
It's a village.
- I love it.
- You...
(The siblings love the sea village.)
- It's a neighborhood.
- Hello.
The alley is so pretty.
(When they enter the attractive alley...)
Look, they drew murals...
on the walls.
- I like stuff like this.
- Me too.
It's so pretty.
It's really pretty.
The street name is Jageungae-gil, which means "small dog street."
- Jageungae-gil?
- Jageungae-gil.
There's a cute dog.
How cute.
(They really have small dogs too.)
Let's take a picture.
(They take a family picture in their first village.)
One, two, three.
I can't open my eyes.
It's fine. Let's go.
We have a long way to go.
(Thanks to non-sentimental Jung Ah, they quickly disband.)
(But...)
The house is located at a rather difficult place.
Goodness.
It doesn't end here.
Are we at the right place?
What?
(The uphill doesn't end.)
Did we walk past it?
How far do we need to go?
(How far do we need to climb?)
This is...
(Looking around)
- In front of our house...
- Wait.
should be a small scooter or a bicycle.
Where is it? Oh, here.
We're here.
(He spots the bicycle.)
(Scurrying)
(He rushes back to carry the others' stuff.)
- It says "The Siblings' House."
- It's cute.
- Help her.
- It's okay.
- It's cute.
- "The Siblings' House."
I'll enter.
(The Siblings' House)
The bicycle is so cute.
- My gosh.
- What an amazing view.
(Clapping)
(Welcome to the Sibling's House.)
The house looks so nice.
(Mint windows which look like the sea of Tongyeong)
Fresh off the Sea always has a door like this.
(Peonies and the sea filling up their front yard)
Gosh, will you look at that?
I can't believe such a house exists.
- Jung Ah, it smells so good.
- It's amazing.
Expensive flowers.
(Expensive flowers?)
- Are these expensive?
- Yes.
(She sniffs the expensive flowers.)
(Ecstatic)
The rooftop?
(From the rooftop, you can see...)
(the blue sea.)
What an amazing view.
We can lay out a mat here...
and drink makgeolli.
Makgeolli!
Makgeolli.
It looks like the sea village house...
which I used to live in when I was young.
(It brings back Sun Young's memories of when she was young.)
(A new season,)
(they will make new memories...)
(in the peony house in Tongyeong.)
(Smiles will bloom on their faces in this house.)
I love it here. What should I do?
How do you do it?
(Huddled together in the big living room)
- I don't know.
- What is this?
My goodness.
It's so nice.
It's my first time seeing this.
It's my first time seeing a turntable.
Me too.
(She turns up the volume a bit.)
- What is it?
- I'm so happy.
- It's so nice.
- It has a nice vibe.
We turned up the volume a bit and then cheered.
There are mosquitoes already.
- Insects.
- Gosh, we need a swatter.
(She killed both the mosquito and the vibe.)
(They settle into the house with music and a mosquito.)
Let's put the groceries into the fridge.
The flower vase.
(Taking out)
(Grinning)
(You Seok's flower gift melts her non-sentimental heart.)
Gosh, look at what You Seok brought.
He went to a flower market yesterday to buy this.
- They're so pretty.
- My gosh.
Our house is full of flowers.
Did he buy flowers? They're pretty.
Where should we put this? Do we have a vase?
Thank you.
Then here.
Let's put it in a coffee pot.
(When you don't have a vase...)
Watch your hand.
(Cutting)
(He skillfully cuts off the neck of the bottle.)
(He fills it up with water.)
(He carefully delivers it to Jung Ah.)
(0 durability, 100 romantic, You Seok's one-and-only vase)
The water has already...
- I put them in water last night.
- Still,
they're pretty fresh.
(Humming at the flower gift)
(Careful)
(Jung Ah moves them one by one into the vase.)
(The man who gave her flowers)
Goodness.
(Focused)
Are you sure you didn't learn this?
- You have good taste.
- I didn't learn at all.
You have an eye for arranging them.
I don't.
(Laughing)
- You have good taste...
- Those who do flower arrangement...
- in aesthetics.
- would laugh at it.
(As he stares blankly at Jung Ah's flower arrangement...)
(He's starting to get bored.)
Shall we go ride a luge?
- Do you have money?
- We don't.
- We have five dollars left.
- We don't have money.
I want to ride a luge and a cable car.
Since we came all the way to Tongyeong.
That was such a mind-blowing question.
"Do you have money?"
(Humble)
What labor will we get to do tomorrow?
That question made me feel so small.
"Do you have money?"
I don't.
For now...
(Meanwhile, Sun Young is making cold coffee.)
Let's make Jung Ah's first.
(Special note: She loves Jung Ah so much.)
Is it too strong?
Jung Ah.
(She calls Jung Ah immediately.)
Try it first.
Shall I make it milder?
- This is just nice.
- Is it okay?
Thank you.
Sun Young.
This is crazy.
It taste better than the ones they sell in coffee shops.
I'll have instant coffee.
- Instant coffee?
- I really shouldn't, though.
I already had two today.
- I'll have one more.
- Sun Young.
Let me just have one more.
- But it...
- This is why I can't lose weight.
Isn't it so nice and sweet?
That's true.
(But...)
(there's no hot water.)
There's no water. It's okay.
- Should I teach you the way?
- What is it?
When you want to make coffee...
but there's no water... You hear the sound?
It's heated up.
- Like this.
- What?
It's heated up.
- Look, Yoon Seo.
- Sun Young.
Look, Yoon Seo. Just like that.
Isn't it fascinating? You don't need to boil it.
You didn't know, did you?
Because the pot is still hot.
Is this funny?
If it doesn't make the sound, it means it doesn't work anymore.
What's so funny about this?
Yoon Seo.
I've kept this secret for 50 years.
Exactly. What a secret.
(Laughing)
Sun Young.
It's because I already feel so close to you.
- We've grown too close.
- You saying silly things?
Yes.
(Meanwhile, You Seok...)
(Groaning)
(Grunting)
(Glancing)
The camera follows me to my sleep.
(Feeling self-conscious...)
(or not.)
(The aftermath of the first labor rushes to him when he lies down.)
I hope it rains.
Rain?
Jung Ah wants to work, basically.
Sitting around doing nothing tires me out.
I need to be always doing something.
(Doing something 1. Standing up and singing)
(Doing something 2. Looking at the mirror)
If you give me free time, I spend all of it looking in the mirror.
(My dear)
(Don't do anything)
Isn't it "don't worry about anything?"
I'll start on another pitch.
(Please don't do anything)
- Don't worry about anything.
- Don't do anything?
See you.
We'll catch a lot of fish using the fish trap.
We're off.
Is that your hat?
- What?
- Is that your hat?
- Yes. You Seok...
- I don't have any.
- Jung Ah.
- You can't put sunscreen like that.
How else do I apply it?
- That's horrible.
- Her hat matches well...
with your outfit.
You Seok, do that while looking in the mirror.
I mean...
Are you going to play golf? My goodness.
(Laughing)
(Tapping)
(While You Seok melts the sunscreen, Yoon Seo prepares the fish trap.)
- Sun Young.
- Yes?
After we set up the fish trap,
let's go on a drive.
- A drive?
- Yes.
- Not with a car.
- Then with a motorcycle?
Bicycle?
You haven't been on the boat yet.
- You should get a boat ride today.
- A drive on a boat?
- Please get ready.
- That sounds good. Okay.
For now...
- Salute.
- You don't want to go out?
- Today...
- I do. I've been dreaming about it.
See you later, Sun Young.
- Salute.
- Are you okay?
Yes.
- Jung Ah.
- Yes?
When they come back from setting up the fish trap,
they want to ride bikes.
They want to go on a bike ride.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Have you used this trap before?
- No.
I only did it when I was young, so I don't remember clearly.
- Do we have bait?
- It's inside here.
There are meat and fish.
- Okay.
- Which one do you want?
- I want meat.
- Then I'll use fish bait.
Let's see which one catches more.
This path is so cute.
We're at our sea again
(The path to the sea became more familiar.)
I love this kind of nature. It's fascinating.
(Surrounded by the mysterious and endless nature)
It smells like the sea.
(A beginner's guide to life in a fishing village: Trap fishing)
- If one of us catches more, - Who catches more?
- let's make...
- The loser goes in the water?
Why do you keep talking about that?
- What will the loser do?
- You want to go in the water?
(The trap fishing siblings settle down at the pier.)
Isn't it nice?
Oh, my.
(Sniffing the fish bait)
I don't even know how to do it.
It doesn't smell that bad.
It needs to smell stronger. That's how it attracts more fish.
I'll put in as much as possible.
(The trap fishing beginner is fully focused.)
We get to do everything possible at the sea.
Right.
(The next task is writing wishes on the fish trap.)
"Yoon Seo."
"Fresh off the Sea becomes..."
"a huge hit."
"Hope it catches a lot."
(Carefully pouring their wishes into every word)
Do you see it clearly?
(Carefully tying to the trap to deliver it to the Sea King)
Do we tie this to the fish trap?
- All right. Are you ready, Yoon?
- Are you done?
I'm ready, Seok.
Do I go first? You go first.
- I haven't done it before.
- This is...
I hope that it catches something so that we can eat.
(Yoon Seo also throws it hard like You Seok.)
(A refreshing fish trap dive)
I hope we catch a lot.
(What kind of friends will show up in the youngest members' trap?)
It's beautiful.
It's drawn with acrylic painting.
It's called Sopo Village.
Why Sopo Village? Does it mean a lot of packages come here?
What does "Sopo" mean?
(What does "Sopo" mean?)
I thought I misheard you.
My goodness.
(Meanwhile, the siblings are preparing for a mysterious drive.)
Aren't I wearing too many colors?
- You look beautiful.
- Do I look okay?
Okay.
You should keep your neck warm.
(And the most excited...)
(mastermind behind the drive)
(Carefully choosing the perfect pair of sunglasses)
(When is he coming out?)
Shall we listen to some music?
(Playing the Top 100 hits to raise the energy)
I like that.
(Dancing immediately to a song that she recognizes)
What is she saying?
For you guys, the lyrics might sound like an alien language.
- Who is it?
- I don't know.
It's an idol group.
Zero, zero.
(Music is all about the spirit.)
(No idea what they're singing, but just dance along)
Moving around makes my back hurt less.
This is nice.
(As they dance with excitement)
It's the sea.
- We're here.
- Thank you for driving.
(They arrive at the port.)
It must be that type of boat.
(What will be today's ride for the four siblings?)
(An outboard motor boat to roam the waters of Tongyeong)
(Simple and easy to operate)
(Anyone with a driver's license can operate it without any certificate.)
(Not only can you cruise the waters of Tongyeong by yourself)
(Self-driving boats are also popular among those who enjoy boat fishing.)
- Is this it?
- Yes.
(Getting on first quickly,)
(the 3rd eldest escorts the eldest aboard 1st.)
- Gosh.
- Thank you.
- I like your socks.
- Thank you, Mr. Driver.
- I'll try driving it.
(Today's captain You Seok takes a seat.)
- You Seok.
- Yes?
We should take a photo of You Seok.
My gosh. This is amazing.
- You Seok, take this.
- I don't want medicine.
- Go on and take it.
- I'm a man.
- I don't take medicine.
- What if you throw up later?
- What is it?
- He's a man, so he won't take it.
- What medicine is it?
- Motion sickness medicine.
- Motion sickness medicine?
- Yes.
(A real man on a boat doesn't need medicine.)
I don't take motion sickness pills.
I never get seasick.
(A captain with serious confidence in his sea legs)
- I'll show you how to operate it.
- Okay.
When you use it, you need to lower the engine first.
You must lower it. There's a button here.
- Press the lower one.
- It's going down.
You have to lower the engine.
- That's it.
- Yes.
Press down and move forward to advance.
- Lower it to move back.
- Lower it all the way to move back.
(It's very easy.)
I got it.
(Mastered it perfectly just in 1 minute)
Is everyone ready?
- Yes, let's go.
- Please set out.
- We're ready.
(Then we'll depart.)
(Click)
See you in a while.
(It was carried out safely with all cast wearing...)
(life jackets and following safety protocols.)
(The outboard boat slowly begins to move.)
Keep turning.
(Towards the sea)
- Is it similar to driving a car?
- I think so.
(Advancing smoothly)
- Is it like driving a car?
- It is,
but you have to use both hands.
You have to use both hands?
(I will still give you a nice ride.)
(Bold and confident steering)
Gosh, the sunlight is intense.
(Racing toward the waters of Tongyeong)
(The siblings' outboard boat smoothly glides across the sea.)
(This is exciting.)
I like it.
It feels like we're floating on water because it sits low.
This is nice.
Hello!
(A completely different view of the sea from when they're working)
This is fun.
(A perfectly healing ride that won their hearts)
Girls, why don't we take a photo?
One, two, three.
(A commemorative photo cannot be missed.)
I feel like we're the only ones here.
- It's so beautiful.
- I feel like I'm rich.
- I feel like...
- Like we're on a yacht.
(A moment that rivals the luxury of any yacht)
The weather is so beautiful.
(After cruising for a while, the captain relaxes.)
Nice.
What's today's sailing route?
Do you see that white lighthouse over there?
- Yes.
- We're heading there.
Okay.
We're heading there.
(Why is he talking like that?)
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
If you're ready, scream.
(Screaming)
(They love it.)
You've done this before, haven't you?
You Seok, you sound like a real captain.
(The captain's way of speaking feels strangely familiar.)
- Actually, he was a captain.
- He really was.
I had a captain's spirit inside me.
(I didn't know about it.)
(I, Kang You Seok)
(My captain's spirit is rising.)
(A true man of the sea, at his best on the boat)
The boat is quite stable.
(Steady and unwavering, in charge of today's voyage)
(I'm Captain Kang, the master of the sea.)
(His jacket is puffed up as much as his confidence.)
You can count on me.
(You can count on me.)
My goodness.
(His enthusiastic fans appear.)
The wind... Captain, could you turn around?
Oh, my.
The weather is really beautiful.
(Captain Kang knows how to treat his fans.)
Captain, you're taking the longer route...
because we're so pretty, right?
Normally, I would've returned a long time ago.
I don't even work this late.
(Encouraged by the positive reaction, he got more smug.)
Captain, where do you live?
The entire Tongyeong is my home.
(Cheeky)
He's really good.
He suddenly got the hang of it.
(A man who's almost too perfect as a captain)
Captain, I bet you were very popular when you were young.
Back in my day...
(Groaning)
People lined up just to get on my boat.
(A handsome captain who had countless women swooning)
They practically lined up.
(My goodness)
- Look how shameless he is.
- I think...
He used his boat to charm women.
Gosh, he's turning.
(I'm feeling good. Let's kick it up a notch.)
(The rugged man of the sea makes a turn to show off.)
(A complete 180 from the start, charging ahead at full speed)
It's the white lighthouse.
(While cruising the sea with the captain)
(they already reached their destination.)
Captain, are you going to turn around?
(Disappointed)
Reversing.
(Putting it in reverse)
(The cheers of fangirls echo across the Tongyeong sea.)
- My goodness.
- Gosh.
- Are you having fun?
- Yes.
No, please!
Gosh.
(A wild U-turn)
My goodness.
- No, mister.
- That's cold.
(A port turn that makes the ladies' hearts race)
Shall we go fast?
(Giggling)
Captain, you're the best.
How about one more ride?
Yes.
(The devoted fans are absolutely thrilled.)
Captain, will you do this for us again next year?
Come back tomorrow. I'll give you another ride.
(Next year is too far away.)
Tomorrow, it will be free.
(The ladies go wild over the VIP treatment on their return visit.)
Captain, you need to make money too.
When I give a ride to pretty ladies,
I feel good even if I don't make money.
(The more they get to know him, the more he's their type.)
Captain, we're having sea squirt doenjang jjigae...
and brisket for dinner tonight. Would you like to join us?
- Can I come over?
- Yes.
(I'd love to come.)
Are you out of your mind?
- You can't invite him over.
- Why not?
The lady with pink sunglasses. You don't like me, do you?
(The sassy Seoul girl with pink sunglasses)
Goodness.
Ladies, if you look over there and wave,
they'll take a photo of you.
If we look over there and wave, they'll take a photo of us.
(With the dashing captain)
Captain, it's sad to leave.
Come back again tomorrow.
(Saying goodbye to the captain with hopes to see him again)
- Let's go home.
- Let's go.
- You Seok, I'll drive.
- I had fun driving.
(Yoon Seo is driving instead of You Seok.)
- I'm having a lot of fun.
- Me too.
- Yes, it's great.
- Actually, I was a bit scared.
- About driving the boat?
- Everything.
- Everything we did today...
- I see.
- including harvesting sea squirts.
- Now that you've done it...
It's fun.
It was fun to clean sea squirts...
for the first time.
I see.
- Yoon Seo, are you having fun too?
- Yes, I'm having a lot of fun.
I see.
- It's so good to hear...
- That's cute.
- that you're having fun.
- I agree.
It's a lot of fun.
I get to try everything that I couldn't normally do.
- It's important that you have fun.
- They're very...
- positive, innocent, and kind.
- They have pure hearts.
I'm so happy to hear that you're enjoying yourselves.
- They're bright and genuine.
- Right.
(It was even more enjoyable as the four siblings were together.)
Once we arrive and cook fast,
we'll be done in an hour.
- We'll be able to eat in an hour.
- Yes.
I'm excited for dinner.
- I think I will really enjoy it.
- It will be good.
We're here.
- Thank you.
- Well done.
- Thank you for driving.
Doesn't it feel like we're back home?
(Soon, it's painted in warm shades of orange.)
(Sopo Village in Tongyeong)
(With the sunset comes dinnertime.)
(What kind of seasonal dishes are the neighbors preparing today?)
(Follow me, meow.)
(Sopo Village leader, Song Ok Ja's house)
I already seasoned it with salt.
Now, just slice it like this.
Add crushed garlic.
Chop some carrots into small pieces and add them.
Add some chili powder.
(Season it with chili powder and Cheongyang chili pepper)
There shouldn't be any excess water. That's the key.
(The neighbor's dish 1: Seasoned sea squirt salad)
(Another seasonal ingredient from Tongyeong)
(Wild rock seaweed)
In Tongyeong,
we mix seaweed with bean sprouts.
Ground sesame, sesame oil.
(Seasoned with ground sesame, sesame oil, and tuna fish sauce...)
This is how we usually eat it.
(It's mixed to create a nutty and mild flavor.)
(The neighbor's dish 2)
(Seasoned rock seaweed and bean sprouts)
(A seasonal table by Song Ok Ja...)
(that's filled with the fresh aroma of Tongyeong's sea)
(Seasoned sea squirt salad, seasoned rock seaweed and bean sprouts...)
(What will the siblings' seasonal table feature today?)
(Grown in the clean water of the southern coast)
(Dinner prepared with fresh sea squirts)
What's on today's menu?
- Sea squirt doenjang jjigae.
- Doenjang jjigae.
We'll make doenjang jjigae with sea squirt.
There's also brisket.
- We bought some brisket.
- We'll grill sea squirts...
in the oil left from cooking brisket.
Right.
(A special transformation of sea squirts, normally enjoyed raw)
(Shall we start preparing dinner?)
Jung Ah, show me how to prepare the radish.
We'll cut the radish outside,
- so take it outside.
- Okay.
(For dinner tonight and a side dish for tomorrow morning)
(Preparing radish and cabbage kimchi first)
Gosh, it's big.
- First...
- Show me once, and I'll do it.
First,
we're going to season it with salt.
Before seasoning it with salt,
cut it like this.
(For radish and cabbage kimchi, slice the radish diagonally.)
- Like that?
- It shouldn't be so thick.
We're going to eat it tomorrow.
This is too thin.
- You know what I mean?
- Yes.
(This is easy enough.)
- I can do it, Jung Ah.
- Yes.
Jung Ah, what other ingredients should we wash...
or prepare?
Spring onions?
We have to wash all the spring onions.
(Sun Young starts chopping with confidence.)
(Missing)
(Struggling)
(Just in 1 second, she gets stuck on slicing the radish.)
(Embarrassed)
- You Seok.
- Yes?
Can you come here for a second?
I'll be right there.
You Seok.
(Captain Yum appears instead of You Seok.)
- What do you need?
- It's okay, Jung Ah.
(Startled)
- What do you need?
- It's okay, Jung Ah.
It's okay, Jung Ah.
- What?
- It's nothing.
- Is it not working?
- I got it.
It's perfect.
- Watch out for your hands.
- Yes?
It's okay, You Seok.
- What?
- I figured it out.
Watch out for your hands.
I can do it well.
I figured it out.
As soon as I saw Jung Ah, I figured it out.
When I saw Jung Ah's face,
a lot of strength appeared from myself.
I definitely had no strength left.
But the instant I saw her face, I suddenly found strength.
Then the knife went in.
She's an amazing person.
That's so funny.
(She may not be resourceful, but she's quick with her hands.)
(She calms down and focuses on slicing the radish.)
Is radish the best in autumn?
This is not what Jung Ah likes.
(The radish is cut too straight.)
(Cutting)
(She starts shaping it the way Jung Ah likes.)
I have to shape it like this.
(Eating)
(She gets rid of the evidence by eating the pieces.)
I have to make it the way she likes. Like radish and cabbage kimchi.
(While shaping it the way Jung Ah likes,)
(she probably eats more than what she shapes.)
This is more like radish kimchi. This won't work.
(Will her radish be okay?)
You know the chungmu gimbap type, right? Like this.
I'm done.
But...
What's wrong, Jung Ah?
- Let me do it again.
- It's too big.
- It's too big? Okay.
- Goodness.
Wait, I'll do it again.
- Jung Ah, is it too big?
- It's big.
We're eating it tomorrow.
If it's this big, when will it ever be ready?
(A brutal scolding)
Wait, I'll make them smaller.
(Wait, I'll make them smaller.)
(An emergency reduction surgery)
- Isn't this okay?
- Yes.
- You're doing well.
Nice.
(Her radish for radish and cabbage kimchi is approved.)
(Let's season the radish with salt.)
We're going to use it in doenjang jjigae.
Okay.
(And...)
(she's adding starch syrup?)
Gosh, starch syrup and...
(Even vinegar?)
I add salty, sour, and sweet flavors.
- My goodness.
- After adding all these,
let it sit in salt for an hour.
My goodness. I had no idea that you add starch syrup.
That's really fascinating.
You don't add it when you make ordinary kimchi.
You don't add starch syrup?
You add starch syrup and vinegar to radish and cabbage kimchi?
We're going to use it to make chungmu gimbap.
We'll cover it...
- and let it sit for an hour.
- Okay.
(Captain Yum is making seasoning for radish and cabbage kimchi.)
Garlic.
Salted shrimp.
(Adding salted shrimp)
Add a tiny bit of anchovy sauce.
Green plum syrup.
(Chef Yum's Tip 1)
(Instead of glutinous rice paste, adding cooled rice)
(Chef Yum's Tip 2)
(Instead of a pear for the refreshing flavor,)
(you can use a pear drink.)
(Blend everything together until smooth.)
That's good.
(The seasoning is ready for making radish and cabbage kimchi.)
(Let's mix it with radish.)
(Coating the radish with chili powder)
(Why chili powder is added separately despite the seasoning)
(Chili powder helps the seasoning cling evenly...)
(to the radish and gives kimchi its signature spicy kick.)
(Adding spring onions)
(Adding the seasoning she made in advance)
(Mixing thoroughly)
(When Chef Yum's special touch is added)
(It looks so good that you want to eat it with some white rice.)
(A bite to see if it turned out well)
(Spicy and crunchy)
You Seok.
(Since it's tasty, the third eldest gets a bite.)
- It's good.
- Is it good?
(Gasping)
That's amazing.
- Yoon Seo.
- Yes?
(She also gives a bite to the youngest.)
Isn't it a little salty?
- It's so good.
- Is it?
- It's so good, Jung Ah.
- Is it? I'm glad.
I can't believe...
I get to taste your food.
I've really wanted to try it.
Yoon Seo, which container would you like the kimchi in?
I'll do it.
- Kimchi?
- Yes. Just give me the plate,
and I'll plate it.
(The youngest shows off her skills as an art student.)
(Since it's Jung Ah's first cooking in Tongyeong...)
I think...
either this or this.
Is this prettier?
Which one do you prefer?
Here.
(She puts just enough kimchi for them to eat today...)
(onto the plate chosen by the youngest.)
(She puts the remaining kimchi into a kimchi container.)
(It will be in charge of their breakfast the next day.)
(Meanwhile...)
(Sun Young wanders about to find something to do.)
Chilies. Tofu.
(She finds some dishes to wash.)
(She washes them immediately.)
You must clean up as you go.
That's how you can sleep early.
(She quickly arranges the piled-up plates.)
(The blender Jung Ah left to soak...)
(after making radish and cabbage kimchi)
(She scrubs it clean.)
(She may not be good at cooking, but she's excellent at cleaning.)
We should recycle, right?
(Neat)
Sun Young is a lot faster...
and better at her tasks than I thought.
- She's super fast.
- She's very fast.
(I'll just do a third of this.)
(Okay.)
(She washes the ingredients without being asked.)
(But she's not exactly thorough.)
(She cuts fast too.)
(I should clean up.)
(She works nonstop.)
(A wasp at work, Sun Young)
(She's even dressed like a wasp.)
(Because of Sun Young,)
(I got a lot faster too.)
(Wasp Sun Young makes impatient Jung Ah rush even more.)
(Look forward to Wasp Sun Young.)
- You Seok, start the fire.
- Okay.
(Is now the time...)
(to show off my manly side?)
(Putting down)
(I can handle holding the fire with my hands.)
I think the fire will get strong rather quickly.
(He pretentiously searches for the next target.)
This.
(Surprised)
(Taken back)
Gosh, this...
(Grunting)
(The cauldron is too heavy for him.)
It's so heavy.
(Waddling)
(He overcomes the weight and places it on the brazier.)
Actually,
it's my first time igniting a fire, and it's burning well.
It's easy to start a fire. It's not hard.
(Acting cocky)
(Let's start with thin-sliced pork belly.)
(He starts...)
(by checking the temperature.)
(He starts grilling.)
(The smoke slowly fills up the front yard.)
(Smoke filter on)
(He cannot breathe.)
(Am I doing it right?)
My eyes sting.
(The cause is the smoke hole being closed.)
(Struggling)
(Unaware of the reason, he showers in the smoke.)
My eyes sting.
(Save You Seok.)
(The first harsh side of the show makes him dizzy.)
My eyes sting.
(This won't do.)
(Sunglasses on)
(He wears a glasses shield and tries again.)
(Defense power 0.1)
(Sizzling)
(Please grill well.)
(Recoiling)
(A drop of tear...)
(for a piece of pork belly)
I'm so sad.
(He fights with the smoke and tries to avoid it.)
(He's met with a harsh welcome.)
Why am I the only one with stinging eyes?
(Confused)
Are you okay?
You don't look okay, but are you okay?
I'm okay.
(I'm okay.)
(Laughing awkwardly)
(He pulls himself together and goes back to grilling.)
(Thanks to You Seok fighting through tears,)
(thin-sliced pork belly is being grilled nicely.)
(The meat warrior fights against the smoke.)
(Meanwhile, Sun Young is taking out some sea squirts to grill.)
That's enough.
(Wash the sea squirts in water before grilling.)
I'll put them in a strainer...
(Ready to deliver with the water drained out)
and deliver them to him.
Boss, I brought some sea squirts.
Sun Young.
(Before grilling the sea squirts, try the meat.)
It's so good.
- Isn't it hot?
- Not at all.
(Feeling proud)
(He puts the well-grilled pork belly onto a plate.)
The oil would splatter like crazy.
(Sea squirt, let's get you an oil shower.)
(Cautious)
(Startled)
(He had collected pork belly oil to grill sea squirts.)
(He quickly adds all the sea squirts to avoid the oil splatter.)
(How will sea squirts taste when grilled using pork belly oil?)
They look like tripe when grilled.
(Sea squirts are getting cooked coated in savory pork belly oil.)
(Once they're cooked, take them out onto a plate before they get tough.)
I'm curious.
It smells so good.
(They blend in nicely with savory pork belly oil.)
This is so fascinating.
(The sea flavor has become even richer.)
I want to try.
(Swallowing her saliva)
- Don't they look like tripe?
- Yes. They look so tasty.
(I can't hold myself back.)
(She blows it and takes a bite.)
Come here.
(How does sea squirt grilled in pork belly oil taste?)
It's delicious.
It has the texture of tripe.
(This feels like tripe!)
It's delicious.
I find this better than the raw one.
(It tastes better than raw sea squirt.)
I should check if the potatoes are cooked.
You haven't added them yet, right?
- Doenjang? I've added it.
- Sea squirts.
I'll put them last.
(Boiling doenjang jjigae as the broth)
(She adds some minced garlic.)
(And anchovy sauce?)
(Chef Yum's tip: Add anchovy sauce...)
(to seafood doenjang jjigae for better umami.)
(Adding some chili powder to make it spicy)
(It already looks delicious.)
(Glancing)
(Surprised)
- It looks good.
- There's a lot.
(The fangirl is looking forward to Jung Ah's doenjang jjigae already.)
It looks good.
It smells amazing.
(She gives her a special tasting service.)
I need to add tofu and other stuff.
- It's good.
- Is it okay?
Is it bland or anything?
(Not at all. Never.)
It's so good.
(I want to eat it with rice already.)
It's going to be good.
(She adds tofu, a must-add ingredient for doenjang jjigae.)
(Today's main ingredient)
(She adds the sea squirts from Tongyeong, the southern coast.)
(Chef Yum's tip: Add sea squirts at the end...)
(to retain their texture and the sea flavor.)
(Add green onions and Cheongyang chili pepper...)
(and let it come to a boil.)
Doenjang jjigae. It smells awesome.
(How does her first sea squirt doenjang jjigae taste?)
(She gives it a pass.)
(Sea squirt doenjang jjigae...)
(using Tongyeong's seasonal sea squirts is completed.)
(Making bibim ramyeon to eat with it)
This is a lot.
(It already looks delicious.)
(Yoon Seo finishes off the bibim ramyeon.)
(The kick is the lettuce topping taken straight from the garden.)
Plating.
(Exclaiming)
You're good at plating.
I know nothing about that. I'm just winging it.
- She was an art major for a reason.
- Exactly.
She majored in art for a reason.
Don't connect this to my major.
(They tease her affectionately.)
I'm so embarrassed.
- Show us your artistic flair.
- I feel pressured.
(Patting)
(With the eggs on top, the colors harmonize well.)
(Their first dinner table is packed with food.)
(Let us tell you about today's dinner.)
(Thin-sliced pork belly that You Seok grilled in tears)
(Grilled sea squirt cooked in pork belly fat)
(A bounty of the ocean in a savory doenjang broth)
(Sea squirt doenjang jjigae)
(Sweet and sour bibim noodles, elevated by the art major)
(And Captain Yum's special radish and cabbage kimchi)
- Good job. Thank you for the meal.
- Thank you for the meal.
- Good job, everyone.
- Enjoy.
(Her mouth is watering.)
(Everything looks delicious.)
- Oh, dear.
- Thank you for the food.
This is... Hold on.
- This is for Yoon Seo.
- Yoon Seo.
- This is for You Seok.
- It's for me.
(Shall we start eating with cool beer?)
- Shall we clink our cans?
- Let's do that.
- Cheers. Good job, everyone.
This is our first dinner.
- This is so good. I love it.
- Nice.
It's good. It's so refreshing.
I feel much better now.
- This beer is so good.
- It's really good.
I thought they only brewed dark beer, but they make lager too.
This brand is famous for its dark beer. It's good.
I feel much better now.
This beer goes down smoothly. It's smooth.
- This beer is good.
- It's so good.
(Now that we've quenched our thirst, shall we start eating?)
(A new twist on sea squirts, which are usually eaten raw)
(How does it taste?)
Oh, my. Hey, the sea squirt is so tasty.
- The grilled sea squirt is good.
- Yes.
Grilling it gave it a texture similar to tripe...
and toned down the fishy flavor. I think it's tasty.
(The sea squirts developed a chewy texture and became less fishy.)
It goes perfectly with beer. Right?
(She has another bite right away.)
(It suits Jung Ah's taste perfectly.)
I'll try it too.
It's good.
(She tries grilled sea squirt for the first time.)
It's so good. It tastes like tripe.
- Tripe with a hint of the ocean.
- Right?
(Chewy)
The scent of the sea squirt kicks in on the finish.
And it's so good.
This is a great way to cook sea squirts...
for those who don't eat them raw.
(Grilled sea squirt would be perfect for those who don't eat them raw.)
It's good.
(Grilling sea squirts reveals a completely different appeal.)
I'll eat the pork belly that I cooked.
It's good.
- Oh, my.
- It's tasty.
- The meat is good.
- Try this.
(It's cooked to perfection.)
Both thin-sliced pork belly and grilled sea squirt...
- go well with beer. It's so good.
- Indeed.
(She especially likes the grilled sea squirt.)
I was so hungry. This is so tasty.
(All my effort and tears paid off.)
I'm so curious about this sea squirt doenjang jjigae.
(How does sea squirt doenjang jjigae taste?)
I'm so curious.
It still has a hint of sea squirts, but it's okay.
(It's good!)
(You Seok has a bite of sea squirt doenjang jjigae too.)
The sea squirt doenjang jjigae is absolutely amazing.
(Really? Is it tasty?)
I mean it. It suits my taste perfectly.
I'm curious.
(Out of curiosity, Yoon Seo tries the sea squirt doenjang jjigae too.)
Jung Ah.
- Is it good?
- It's so good.
- It's good. It's also a bit spicy.
- It's still good with sea squirts.
The combination of the sea squirts and chili...
brings a hint of the ocean...
- and a pleasant kick.
- It does have a nice kick.
(The spiciness keeps him coming back for more.)
The jjigae is really good.
The scent of the sea squirt kicks in on the finish.
This is so tasty.
(This time, he mixes some rice into the broth.)
(Yoon Seo is also in love with the sea squirt doenjang jjigae.)
(Oh, sea squirt doenjang jjigae, how tasty you are.)
- It's so good.
- It's really good.
I should've watched you cook.
- Oh, I can just catch it on TV.
- I'll give you the recipe.
- I'll share it with you.
- Okay.
- Will you try the recipe at home?
- No.
I'm just curious.
(I'll just eat a lot of it here.)
- My, this is so good. It's amazing.
- Right?
(Yoon Seo will try Jung Ah's radish and cabbage kimchi.)
(Crunchy)
- Jung Ah, your kimchi is so good.
- Is it good?
- It'll taste better tomorrow.
- Right. It'll be so good tomorrow.
It's absolutely amazing.
- Is it?
- Yes.
This tastes exactly like fresh kimchi.
(It has a wonderful crunch as it's freshly made.)
(When she eats Jung Ah's radish and cabbage kimchi...)
(and Jung Ah's sea squirt doenjang jjigae...)
My, it's so good.
This is power.
(She raises her eyebrow, acting like a total fangirl.)
Getting to eat Jung Ah's food.
(The symbol of power)
(Jung Ah's dishes made their dinner time so happy.)
Yoon Seo, this is too pretty to eat.
(Yoon Seo showcased her artistic flair with the noodle plating.)
(How does it taste?)
Oh, it's good.
(It passes the taste test.)
(Slurping)
(Yoon Seo eats a piece of thin-sliced pork belly.)
(And then she takes a big bite of the bibim ramyeon.)
- You Seok.
- It's so good.
(You Seok, try the noodles with the meat.)
- What kind of doenjang did you use?
- A regular type of doenjang.
(The combination of thin-sliced pork belly and bibim ramyeon is...)
(the ultimate cheat code.)
(Sun Young picks up a piece of meat first.)
You Seok, thank you for cooking the meat.
(She puts the meat on the vegetables.)
- The noodles...
- I love it.
(Then she covers the meat with a lot of noodles.)
How about I put them together in my vegetable wrap?
(She puts it all in her mouth.)
(Jung Ah watches her eating.)
(It's absolutely delicious.)
- I'm so happy right now.
- Me too.
- Everything is good, and I'm happy.
- I'm relieved.
- You were very hungry, right?
- Yes, I was, but...
I mean, my stomach just felt hollow.
(They cooked with the fresh ingredient they harvested...)
(for their first meal on the show, which makes them even happier.)
It's so good.
(After all their hard work, they earned this happy dinner time.)
Guys, look at the view while eating.
(The scenery makes them lift their heads.)
Isn't it beautiful?
(Behind the peony blooming in the yard,)
(the night sea of Tongyeong is gently swaying.)
It's nice to sit outside...
- Exactly.
- and look at the sea.
All the fatigue of the day just melts away...
thanks to this amazing food.
I thought...
You Seok was a quiet person.
- I told you that wasn't true.
- But he's actually a chatterbox.
- I told you I was chatty.
- I didn't believe you...
- because you didn't talk so much.
- I told you,
I get chatty once I get close to someone.
I told you that. I'll stay quiet again.
You shouldn't.
Right.
(While eating and laughing, they get curious about something.)
I'm so curious to see what's going to happen tomorrow.
They'll tell us.
- They'll tell us, right?
- Yes.
(Looking forward to the announcement)
Is there anything you're expecting?
- I got it.
- Aralia cordata? Horse mackerel?
- Horse mackerel.
- Aralia cordata.
- Aralia cordata?
- They're on our map.
Is one of them correct?
(There are clues on the map?)
(Aralia cordata, horse mackerel)
(They guessed tomorrow's task based on the map.)
- It's one of them.
- The map we have...
Is one of them correct or not?
- Horse mackerel or aralia cordata.
- Aralia cordata.
Aralia cordata.
- We're spot on, aren't we?
- It's aralia cordata, right?
It's aralia cordata.
I'm sure of it.
(We hit the spot, didn't we?)
- Tomorrow, we will...
- Yes?
leave at 11am.
- We have more than enough time.
- That's great.
You will leave at 11am, and when you get there...
(So...)
(What kind of work will we do?)
You will find out about the job.
(Come on.)
You acted like you would tell us.
Gosh. They won't tell us?
Still, leaving at 11am sounds good to me.
Just tell us this one thing. Will we be on a boat or on land?
They won't tell us that either.
I'm sure we won't go out to sea. We headed out on a boat twice today.
Tomorrow will be our third time on a boat.
It won't be fun to watch us on a boat all the time.
- The viewers will get bored.
- We'll be on a boat twice a day.
(Tomorrow's labor remains a mystery.)
So you won't tell us until tomorrow?
(Tomorrow's work remains a mystery.)
(Today is going to be a real grind.)
(Give it your all, like your life depends on it.)
(Like my life depends on it?)
(Screaming)
(Screams break out everywhere.)
(Imagine we're at an OB-GYN.)
(The work is as tough as labor pains?)
(The youngest members get frightened too.)
(It means you won't get paid if you keep going like this.)
(Even their best effort isn't enough to earn their keep.)
(Help!)
(It all happens in the deep sea.)
(What could be the job that frightened the four members?)
(Right then, suspicious person approaches them.)
(I told you not to take the boat out!)
(He scolds the four members?)
(Eun Myeong, Daddy is here!)
(The 1st guest in Season 3, Actor Park Hae Joon)
(You're here, Father.)
(He's Hae Joon, just as I thought.)
(Why didn't you get on the boat?)
(You must work, Hae Joon.)
(I stayed to work even harder later.)
(Meticulous)
(It turns out he's good at hard labor?)
(He's a good dancer too?)
(What is up with him?)
(I'm a shy, middle-aged man.)
(He becomes an excited man around the siblings.)
(He turns out to have a lot of lively energy.)
(I guess I'm a fool)
(You Seok's playful performance...)
(that cracked the older members up will be revealed as well.)
(Stop filming! I said, stop filming!)
(Their happiness didn't last long.)
(What are you trying to do?)
(Have we done something wrong?)
(The siblings got terrified.)
(What threw the siblings into a panic?)